http://www.methodistchapel.co.uk/privacy/

Your eligible deposits with Methodist Chapel Aid Ltd are protected up to a total of £85,000 by the Financial Services Compensation Scheme, the UK's deposit guarantee scheme. Any deposits you hold above the £85,000 limit are unlikely to be covered.
Please click here for further information or visit www.fscs.org.uk.
Close
Toggle navigation
Call us now to discuss your loan
01904 622150
Get a property loan
Deposits
Car loans
About us
Our investment policy
Financial information
Contact us
Privacy
Privacy Notice
We have updated our Privacy Notice in line with new data protection laws (under the General Data Protection Regulation) which came into effect on 25 May 2018.
We take our data privacy responsibilities very seriously, and we want you to understand and feel confident about how we collect, store and handle your personal data.
Our Privacy Notice explains this, and sets out the rights you have in relations to your personal data. We will continue to review the content of our Privacy Notice and any updates to this will be available to view on our website.
Download the full document here.
CookiesThe cookie settings on this website are set to ‘allow all cookies’. Leaving your settings to ‘allow all cookies’ means you consent to a website remembering your preferences and generally enhancing the user experience. If you prefer a website to not remember your preferences, you can change your settings at any time by changing the privacy settings of your browser.Find out more about cookies >
